# Jung, Cheyoon

Date of birth: 05 Dec 1994
Mobile: +36 30 856 1241
Email: jessietwo94@gmail.com
Website: www.jcheyoon.com
Github: github.com/JCheyoon

I majored **Movie Image Design** and worked as a graphic designer for almost 2 years, where I learned to use several design tools. I also got introduced to **the world of IT** and later started to study about software development.

I would like to get more familiar with this industry and work in an atmosphere where I can feel **motivated**.

Keeping up my **professional development** is important for me, while I support my team using the **experiences and soft skills** I brought from my prior positions.

### Working experience

#### Designer, MOON42 RDI Ltd.

Oct 2020 - Sep 2021, Budapest, Hungary

Making animations for promotional videos using After Effects. Drawing vector illustrations using Illustrator.

#### **Data Coordinator, Tumlare Corportation**

Sep 2018 - Oct 2020, Budapest, Hungary

Handling Hotel contracts data. Keeping contact with suppliers and satellite offices.

#### Designer, Fairip

Aug 2017 - Jun 2018, Seoul, Korea

Making animations for promotional videos using After Effects. Taking and Editing videos. Supporting Marketing Management.

### **Strengths**

- Open, expressive personality, usually feel easy to adapt to new environments and tasks
- Single-focus thinking style, but still like to think in high context and see the big picture
- Routine Persistence, Adaptable to tasks requiring repetition, maintaining a commitment to excellence

### What I would like to learn, improve

Software development lifecycle, process



#### **Skills**

#### Main stack:

- > REACT
- > JAVASCRIPT
- > TYPESCRIPT

#### Tech I also use every day:

- ➤ HTML5
- > CSS3 / SCSS
- > GIT
- ➤ React Three Fiber
- > REST APIS

#### I'm also familiar with:

ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS | ILLUSTRATOR | PHOTOSHOP | PREMIERE | CINEMA4D | GITHUB

#### **Education**

#### **Self-learning**

2021 - Present, Various online courses and tutorials of programming and web development

#### **Tower Nyelviskola, Hungary**

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018, English learning

#### Baguio English Communication Institute, Philippines

Feb 2016 - Jul 2016, English learing

## Hyanyang Women University, Seoul

2013- 2015, Movie Image Design

### **Previous Working experiences**

Design Assistant, Harmony Interior

Oct 2015 - Jul 2017, Seoul, Korea

Part-timer, Korea Racing Authority (Part-time)

Aug 2015 - Jan 2016, Seoul, Korea

**Video Editor, SK C&C** (Part-time) Jul 2015 - Aug 2015, Gwangju, Korea

### **Licenses & ertifications**

**Craftsman Computer Graphics Operation** 

Issued Apr 2017, HRD Korea (Credential ID 17401021654T)

**Industrial Engineer Colorist** 

Issued Nov 2014 HRD Korea (Credential ID 14203021293H)

**Graphic Technology Qualification** 

Issued Jul 2014 KPC (GA01G14106240150)

### Languages

#### Korean

Native language

#### **English**

Fluent oral and written skills

#### Hungarian

Basic level

### Hobbies, Range of interests

- Yoga
- Traveling
- Watching TV-shows (sci-fi, fantasy, documentaries)
- Cooking
- Photography, photo editing